Holding the finale of my story close to heart
saihate no story idaite
I continue to wander aimlessly
ate mo naku samayoi tsuzuketa
Within this new world
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
But I feel that spark’s rekindled in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
THIS
IS WHERE
TOMORROW
BRINGS
A NEW GAME
IT'S TIME
TO LEARN
THAT PAIN
IS GAIN
READY?
FIGHT!
Gotta crush my anguish from the past
kako no shitsubou nuritsubusu tame ni
Clear up the dark skies of my future
gisei ni shite kita mirai
Will endeavour ’til I breathe my last
boku no raifu ga tsukiru made
And fight until the bitter end to blow apart destiny
sono sadame buchikowashite iku no sa
Break out and start your revolution
Beyond it I may find my long-sought answer
hitotsu no kotae wo sagashite
I race until I hit my limit
genkai no race ni idonde
No way I’m wasting the final chance I’ve been given!
ichidokiri no chansu to shitte
I’ll persevere and take control of my own destiny
seotta unmei koete yukunda yo
Holding the finale of my story close to heart
saihate no story idaite
I continue to wander aimlessly
ate mo naku samayoi tsuzuketa
Within this new world
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
But I feel that spark’s rekindled in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes