Half asleep still, I open my eyes to the morning sun
mezamete wa kurikaesu nemui asa wa
Tying my tie tight as I rush out the door
eri no tie wo kitsuku shime
Arriving at the classroom, I step through the door
kyoushitsu no door kuguru to honno sukoshi
With my chest slightly puffed up
mune wo hatte arukidaseru
But then a sudden breeze gushed through my regular life
sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
I feel like I can hear it
kikoeta ki ga shita
I can feel it calling out to me
kanjita ki ga shitan da
Firing a beat straight through my heart
furuedasu ima kono mune de
Then it flickers once again
mou kuru ki ga shita
Like the millions of stars dotted across the sky
ikuoku no hoshi ga kiesatteku no wo
I sent it on its way
miokutta
And as I waved goodbye
te wo futta
I cheered it on
yokatta ne to